we ran an experiment on v-j with the
help of his wife deep deep she allowed
us to put a camera in the car to record
how Vijay reacts to different situations
while driving this experiment was to
prove that Vijay commits a lot of
traffic violations but only follows the
rules when there are cops around
Deepti wanted a husband to realize that
he should be more careful while driving
and not just follow the rules for fear
of being caught we also followed them to
see how Vijay reacts to different
situations on the road now let's see how
our experiment turned out Vijay is
driving around without a seatbelt
on seeing cops ahead this is how he
reacts
this is the first signal that they come
across on seeing that there is no cop
let's see what VJ does hello yeah yeah
hullabaloo hey presentation lady
okay we are coming up on a cop what will
Vijay do it sir
I'll call you back you know by my copy
yeah yeah bye ticket no movie be telling
you bus Vijay and Deepti have come back
home now it's time for us to drive a
point home with Vijay lunch the way
favorite a click I'm Linda in a machine
we step out of the car what happen here
we explained to Vijay that his wife had
participated in this experiment to show
him his driving pattern we showed the
recordings of his drive to Vijay to his
credit he accepted responsibility and
promised his wife he'd drive safer and
better it's our turn now to take
responsibility be honest aren't we all
at least a little bit like Vijay if you
agree hit like below and promise
yourself you'll drive more responsibly